Lesson 26. Wanted. A large biscuit tin. No one can avoid being influenced by advertisements.
第26课。想要。大型饼干锡。没有人可以避免受到广告的影响。
pride: v.   骄傲, taste: n.   鉴赏力
Much as we may pride ourselves on our good taste, we are no longer free to choose the things we want.
正如我们可能以自己的良好品味而自豪的那样，我们不再自由选择想要的东西。
exert: v.   施加, subtle: aj.  微妙的，难以捉摸的
For advertising exerts a subtle influence on us. In their efforts to persuade us to buy this
对于广告，对我们产生了微妙的影响。在他们说服我们购买此事的努力中
or that product. Advertisers have made a close study of human nature and have classified all our
或该产品。广告商对人性进行了仔细研究，并将我们所有的所有
little weaknesses. Advertisers discovered years ago that all of us love to get something for nothing.
很少的弱点。广告商几年前发现，我们所有人都喜欢一无所获。
magic: adj. 有奇妙作用
An advertisement which begins with the magic word free can rarely go wrong. These days,
从魔术词免费开始的广告很少会出错。这些日子，
advertiser: n.   做广告的人, sample: n.   样品
advertisers not only offer free samples, but free cars, free houses, and free trips around the
广告商不仅提供免费的样品，而且提供免费的汽车，免费的房屋和免费旅行
devise: v.   设计，想出
world as well. They devise hundreds of competitions which will enable us to win huge sums of money.
世界也是如此。他们设计了数百场比赛，这将使我们能够赢得巨额资金。
advertiser: n.   做广告的人, capture: v.   吸引，赢得
Radio and television have made it possible for advertisers to capture the attention of millions of
广播和电视使广告商有可能吸引数百万的关注
manufacturer: n.   生产厂家，制造商
people in this way. During a radio program, a company of biscuit manufacturers once ask
人们以这种方式。在广播节目中，一家饼干制造商曾经询问
listeners to bake biscuits and send them to their factory. They offered to pay $10
听众烘烤饼干并将其发送到工厂。他们提出要支付10美元
a pound for the biggest biscuit baked by a listener. The response to this competition was tremendous.
一磅为听众烘烤的最大饼干。对这场比赛的反应是巨大的。
Before long, biscuits of all shapes and sizes began arriving at the factory. One lady brought
不久之后，各种形状和尺寸的饼干开始到达工厂。一位女士带来
wheelbarrow: n.   独轮手推车
in a biscuit on a wheelbarrow. It weighed nearly 500 pounds. A little later, a man came along with a
在独轮车上的饼干中。它重近500磅。过了一会儿，一个男人带着一个
boot: n.  （汽车尾部的）行李箱
biscuit which occupied the whole boot of his car. All the biscuits that were sent were carefully
饼干占据了他汽车的整个靴子。所有发送的饼干都仔细
weighed. The largest was 713 pounds. It seemed certain that this would win the price.
称重。最大的是713磅。似乎可以肯定的是，这将赢得价格。
But just before the competition closed, a lorry arrived at the factory with a truly colossal biscuit
但是在比赛结束之前，一辆卡车带着一个真正巨大的饼干到达了工厂
which weighed 2,400 pounds. It had been baked by a college student who had used over 1,000 pounds of
重2400磅。它是由一名使用超过1000磅的大学生烘烤的
ingredient: n.   配料
flour, 800 pounds of sugar, 200 pounds of fat, and 400 pounds of various other ingredients.
面粉，800磅的糖，200磅的脂肪和400磅的其他各种成分。
crane: n.   起重机
It was so heavy that a crane had to be used to remove it from the lorry.
它是如此沉重，以至于必须使用起重机将其从货车上取出。
manufacturer: n.   生产厂家，制造商, anticipate: v.   预期，预料
The manufacturers had to pay more money than they had anticipated.
制造商必须支付的钱比预期的要多。
Are they bought the biscuit from the student for $24,000?
他们是否以24,000美元的价格从学生那里购买了饼干？